Guide to the Western Filmscript Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Western Filmscripts Acquired Before July 1996, 1918-1989
  - Chisum, 1970 release (Box 10, Folder 69)
    Producer: [Andrew J. Fenody]
    Actors: John Wayne Forrest Tucker Christopher George
    Notes: Different characters than released version.
  - Chuka, November 2, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    Story: Richard Jessup
    Screenplay: Richard Fielder [Richard Jessup]
    Director: Gordon Douglas
    Producer: [Rod Taylor Jack Jason]
    Actors: Ernest Borgnine John Mills Luciana Paluzzi
    Production company: Rodlor Productions
    Type: Revised final shooting script
    Notes: "Rod Taylor" on front cover
  - Cimarron, October 22, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 71)
    Screenplay: Arnold Shulman
    Producer: Edmund Grainger
    Actors: Glenn Ford Maria Schell Anne Baxter
    Setting: Oklahoma Territory
    Type: Complete
    Notes: remake of 1931 version
  - Cimarron, October 5, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 72)
    Type: Temporary incomplete
  - Cisco Kid and the Lady, August 26, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 73)
    Screenplay: Frances Hyland
    Director: [Herbert I. Leeds]
    Producer: [John Stone (assoc)]
    Actors: [Cesar Romero Marjorie Weaver Chris-Pin Martin]
    Notes: Cisco Kid series. Working title: The Adventurer
  - City of Badmen (Subtitle: Gunsmoke), October 9, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 74)
    Screenplay: George W. George George F. Slavin
    Director: [Harmon Jones]
    Producer: [Leonard Goldstein]
    Actors: [Jeanne Crain Dale Robertson Richard Boone]
    Setting: 1890, Carson City, Nevada
    Notes: Working title: Gunsmoke
  - The Comancheros, March 23, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 75)
    Story: Paul I. Wellman
    Screenplay: Douglas Heyes [James Edward Grant] [Clair Huffaker]
    Director: [Michael Curtiz] [John Wayne]
    Producer: [George Sherman]
    Actors: [John Wayne Stuart Whitman Ina Balin]
    Setting: 1843, New Orleans, Texas
  - Come and Get It, [1935 release] (Box 11, Folder 76)
    Story: Edna Ferber
    Screenplay: Jane Murfin [Jules Furthman]
    Director: [Howard Hawks] [William Wyler]
    Producer: [Merritt Hulburd]
    Actors: [Frances Farmer Edward Arnold Joel McCrea]
    Production company: [Samuel Goldwyn Productions]
    Notes: Song lyrics bound in the beginning of the script.
  - Compaeros, [1972 release] (Box 11, Folder 77)
    Screenplay: John Amos Mark Miller
    Production company: Bighorn Production Company
    Setting: Texas, 1870s
    Notes: "Struther Martin" on cover. Proposed cast list enclosed.
  - The Court- Martial of George Armstrong Custer, October 10, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 78)
    Story: Douglas C. Jones
    Screenplay: John Gay
    Director: [Glenn Jordan]
    Producer: Norman Rosemont
    Actors: [James Olsen Blythe Danner]
    Production company: Norman Rosemont Productions
    Distributor: Warner Brothers Television
    Type: Second revised draft
  - Cowboy, April 9, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 79)
    Story: [Frank Harris]
    Screenplay: Raphael Hayes [Edmund H. North]
    Actors: [Glenn Ford Jack Lemmon Anna Kashfi]
    Notes: Working Title: Reminiscences of a Cowboy
  - The Cowboys, March 8, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 80)
    Story: William Dale Jennings
    Screenplay: Irving Ravetch Harriet Frank, Jr. [William Dale Jennings]
    Director: [Mark Rydell]
    Producer: [Mark Rydell]
    Actors: [John Wayne Roscoe Lee Brown A. Martinez]
    Production company: Sanford Productions
    Type: Final complete
  - Cutter's Trail, May 31, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 81)
    Screenplay: Paul Savage
    Director: Vincent McEveety
    Producer: John Mantley
    Actors: [John Gavin Manuel Padilla, Jr. Marisa Pavon]
    Production company: CBS Studio Center
    Setting: Santa Fe
    Notes: Call sheet for screen tests enclosed. "Orrel Johnson" written on the cover. Working title: Slaughter's Trail
  - Dances With Wolves, May 23, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 82)
    Screenplay: William Blake
    Director: [Kevin Costner]
    Producer: [Jim Wilson Kevin Costner]
    Actors: [Kevin Costner Mary McDonnell Graham Greene]
    Production company: TIG Productions
    Distributor: Orion Pictures
  - Dark Command, December 1, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 83)
    Screenplay: [F. Hugh Herbert Grover Jones Lionel Hauser]
    Director: [Raoul Walsh]
    Producer: Sol C. Siegel
    Actors: [Claire Trevor John Wayne Walter Pidgeon]
    Setting: Kansas, 1859
    Notes: "Sol C. Siegel" stamped on cover, includes stills
  - Dark Command, [1940 release] (Box 12, Folder 84)
    Screenplay: F. Hugh Herbert Grover Jones Lionel Hauser
    Director: Raoul Walsh
    Actors: Claire Trevor John Wayne Walter Pidgeon
  - The Daughters of Joshua Cabe, April 28, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 85)
    Director: Philip Leacock
    Actors: Buddy Ebsen Karen Valentine Lesley Anne Warren
    Production company: Spelling/Goldberg Productions, ABC-TV
    Distributor: Twentieth Century-Fox Studios
    Notes: ABC Movie of the Week
  - The Daughters of Joshua Cabe Return, August 27, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 86)
    Screenplay: Kathleen Hite
    Director: David Lowell Rich
    Actors: Dan Dailey Dub Taylor Ronnie Troup
    Production company: Spelling/Goldberg Productions
    Setting: Wyoming
    Type: Third revised final
    Notes: ABC Movie of the week, sequel to "The Daughters of Joshua Cabe" "1/28/75" written on cover
  - Dead Man's Trail, [1952 release] (Box 13, Folder 87)
    Screenplay: [Joseph Poland]
    Director: [Lewis D. Collins]
    Producer: [Vincent M. Fennelly]
    Actors: [Johnny Mack Brown Jimmy Ellison Barbara Allen]
    Production company: [Frontier Pictures]
    Notes: Range Busters series.
  - Death Valley Outlaws, August 5, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 88)
    Story: [Don Ryan]
    Screenplay: [Don Ryan Jack Lait, Jr.]
    Actors: [Don Barry Lynn Merrick Milburn Stone]
  - The Desperado, August 17, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 89)
    Story: Clifton Adams
    Screenplay: Geoffrey Homes
    Director: [Thomas Carr]
    Actors: [Wayne Morris James Lydon Beverly Garland]
    Production company: MCA Artists
    Setting: Texas, 1870
  - Desperate Trails, July 24, 1939 (Box 13, Folder 90)
    Screenplay: Andrew Bennison
    Director: Albert Ray
    Producer: Albert Ray (assoc}
    Actors: Johnny Mack Brown Bob Baker Fuzzy Knight
    Setting: Winston Forks
    Type: Continuity and dialogue
  - Destry, September 15, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 91)
    Story: Max Brand
    Screenplay: Edmund H. North D. D. Beauchamp Felix Jackson
    Director: George Marshall
    Producer: Stanley Rubin
    Actors: Audie Murphy Mari Blanchard
    Production company: Universal- International
    Distributor: Universal-International
    Type: Dialogue continuity
  - Devil's Trail, September 18, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 92)
    Story: [Robert Lee Johnson]
    Screenplay: Leon Barsha Robert Lee Johnson
    Director: Lambert Hillyer
    Actors: Bill Elliot Tex Ritter Eileen O'Hearn
    Setting: Kansas, 1855
    Notes: Working title: The Town in Hell's Backyard
  - Dick Turpin, 1925 (Box 14, Folder 93)
    Actors: Tom Mix Kathleen Myers James Marcus
    Type: Synopsis
  - Dirty Harry, September 23, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 94)
    Story: Harry Julian Fink [Rita M. Fink]
    Screenplay: John Milius [Harry Julian Fink Rita M. Fink Dean Riesner]
    Director: [Don Siegel]
    Producer: [Don Siegel]
    Actors: [Clint Eastwood Reni Santoni Harry Guardino]
    Production company: Malpaso
    Setting: Baghdad by the Bay, CA; 1970's
  - Dirty Harry, November 17, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 95)
    Story: [Rita M. Fink Harry Julian Fink]
    Screenplay: Terry Malick John Milius Harry Julian Fink [Rita M. Fink Dean Riesner]
    Setting: Baghdad by the Bay, CA; 1970s
    Notes: Includes script, synopsis, pre- production schedule, etc. In library binding, withdrawn from Emerson College.
  - A Distant Trumpet, May 31, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 96)
    Screenplay: Albert Beich [John Twist Richard Fielder]
    Producer: [William H. Wright]
    Actors: Troy Donahue Suzanne Pleshette
    Setting: Deadlands, 1883
    Type: Revised estimating
  - The Drifter, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 97)
    Story: Oliver Drake
    Screenplay: Oliver Drake
    Director: [William O'Connor]
    Producer: Miles Kent
    Actors: William Farnum [Noah Beery Phyllis Barrington]
    Setting: Missouri
    Notes: Working title: Wanderlust.
  - The Duchess and the Dirtwater Fox, July 23, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 98)
    Story: Barry Sandler
    Screenplay: Melvin Frank Barry Sandler Jack Rose
    Director: Melvin Frank
    Producer: Melvin Frank
    Actors: George Segal Goldie Hawn Conrad Janis
    Type: Second revised final
    Notes: very different from earlier version
  - The Duchess and the Dirtwater Fox, 1976 release (Box 14, Folder 99)
    Screenplay: [Melvin Frank] Barry Sandler [Jack Rose]
    Producer: [Melvin Frank]
  - Duck, You Sucker, June 24, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 100)
    Story: [Sergio Leone Sergio Donati]
    Screenplay: Luciano Vincenzoni
    Director: Sergio Leone
    Producer: Fulvio Morsella
    Actors: Rod Steiger James Coburn Romolo Valli
    Production company: Rafran Cinematografia European International Films
    Type: Combined continuity
    Notes: U.S. version. Filmed in Spain and Italy.
  - Duel in the Sun, February 14, 1945 (Box 15, Folder 101)
    Story: [Niven Busch]
    Screenplay: Oliver H. P. Garrett
    Director: [King Vidor]
    Producer: [David O. Selznick]
    Actors: [Jennifer Jones Joseph Cotten Gregory Peck]
    Production company: Selznick Productions
    Distributor: Vanguard Films
  - The Eagle's Brood, August 10, 1935 (Box 15, Folder 102)
    Screenplay: Doris Schroeder Harrison Jacobs
    Director: [Howard Bretherton]
    Producer: [Harry Sherman]
    Actors: [William Boyd Jimmy Ellison William Farnum]
    Production company: Harry Sherman Productions / Prudential Studios
    Setting: Southwest near Mexico
    Notes: Hopalong Cassidy series.
  - Easy Going, February 6, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 103)
    Screenplay: Byron Morgan Alfred Block
    Setting: Carnival in the West
    Type: Third Draft
  - The Electric Horseman, 1979 release (Box 15, Folder 104)
    Screenplay: Paul Gaer [Robert Garland]
    Director: [Sidney Pollack]
    Producer: [Ray Stark]
    Actors: [Robert Redford Jane Fonda Willie Nelson]
    Production company: Cinema Pacific Corporation
    Distributor: [Columbia/Universal]
    Setting: Present day west
    Notes: Probably first draft sent to CPC.
  - The Empire of the West, November 2, 1943 (Box 15, Folder 105)
  - Every Which Way But Loose, March 17, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 106)
    Screenplay: Jeremy Joe Kronsberg
    Director: [James Fargo]
    Producer: [Robert Daley]
    Setting: Twentieth century California
  - The Executioner's Song, July 24, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 107)
    Story: Norman Mailer
    Screenplay: Norman Mailer
    Actors: [Tommy Lee Jones Goldie Hawn]
    Production company: Laurence Schiller Productions
    Setting: Provo, Utah
    Type: Pre-production draft
    Notes: TV movie re-released in theaters.
  - Eyes of the Forest, 1923 release (Box 16, Folder 108)
    Story: LeRoy Stone
    Screenplay: Shannon Fife
    Producer: Lambert Hillyer
    Actors: Tom Mix Pauline Stark Sid Jordan
  - Fighting for Gold, 1919 (Box 16, Folder 109)
    Screenplay: [W.R. Raine] Charles Kenyon
    Director: [Edward J. Le Saint]
    Producer: Edward J. Le Saint
    Actors: Tom Mix [Jack Nelson Harry Lonsdale]
    Production company: William Fox Studios
    Distributor: William Fox Studios
    Setting: Mining country
    Notes: Silent film. Comments added. Working title: The Highgrader
  - Fighting Valley, [1943 release] (Box 16, Folder 110)
    Director: [Oliver Drake]
    Producer: [Alfred Stern Arthur Alexander]
    Actors: [Dave O'Brien Guy Wilkerson Jim Newill]
    Notes: Texas Rangers series
  - The First Texan, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 111)
    Screenplay: Daniel B. Ullman
    Director: Byron Haskin
    Producer: Walter Mirisch
    Actors: [Joel McCrea Felicia Farr Jeff Morrow]
    Production company: Allied Artists Productions
    Distributor: Allied Artists Productions
    Setting: Texas, 1832
  - Flaming Lead, March 21, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 112)
    Screenplay: Joseph O'Donnell
    Director: Sam Newfield
    Producer: Max Alexander [Arthur Alexander]
    Actors: Ken Maynard [Eleanor Stewart Dave O'Brien]
    Production company: Colony Pictures
    Distributor: Colony Pictures
    Setting: Cattle country
    Notes: With revisions. The story of Sam Houston.
  - For A Few Dollars More (Subtitle: Per Quaiche Dollaro In Piu), October 4, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 113)
    Story: Sergio Leone Fulvio Morsella
    Screenplay: Luciano Vincenzoni Sergio Leone
    Actors: Clint Eastwood Lee Van Cleef Gian Maria Volonte
    Production company: Arturo Gonzales Constantin Film
    Setting: Tucumari
    Type: Cutting and dialogue
  - Forbidden Trails, January 24, 1920 (Box 16, Folder 114)
    Story: Charles Alden Seltzer
    Screenplay: Scott Dunlap
    Director: [Scott Dunlap]
    Producer: Scott Dunlap
    Actors: Buck Jones [Winifred Westover Stanton Heck]
    Setting: mining country
    Notes: Silent film.
  - Fort Apache, July 10, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 115)
    Story: James Warner Bellah
    Screenplay: Frank S. Nugent
    Director: [John Ford]
    Producer: [John Ford Merian C. Cooper]
    Actors: [John Wayne Henry Fonda Shirley Temple]
    Production company: Argosy Pictures
    Distributor: [RKO Radio Pictures]
    Setting: southern Arizona desert
    Type: Revised script
    Notes: Working title: War Party
  - Forty Thieves, November 20, 1943 (Box 17, Folder 116)
    Screenplay: Michael Wilson Bernie Kamins
    Director: Lesley Selander
    Actors: William Boyd Andy Clyde Louise Currie
    Production company: United Artists
    Notes: Hopalong Cassidy series
  - The Frisco Kid, August 16, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 117)
    Screenplay: Michael Elias Frank Shawn
    Director: Dick Richards [Robert Aldrich]
    Producer: Mace Neufeld
    Actors: Gene Wilder Harrison Ford Ramon Bieri
    Setting: 1850
    Type: Shooting schedule
    Notes: Working title: No-Knife
  - The Frisco Kid, October 16, 1978; rev. October 25 1978. (Box 17, Folder 118)
    Director: [Robert Aldrich]
  - Frisco Sal, September 1, 1944 (Box 17, Folder 119)
    Screenplay: Curt Siodmak Gerald Geraghty
    Director: [George Waggner]
    Producer: [George Waggner]
    Actors: [Susanna Foster Turhan Bey Alan Curtis]
    Production company: Universal
    Distributor: Universal
  - Frontier Gunlaw, June 22, 1944 (Box 17, Folder 120)
    Story: [Victor McLeod]
    Screenplay: [Bennett Cohen]
    Director: Derwin Abrahams
    Producer: Colbert Clark
    Actors: [Charles Starrett] Tex Harding Dub Taylor
    Setting: California, 1880
    Notes: Includes shooting schedule. Durango Kid series. Working titles: Prairie Raiders; Phantom Outlaws
  - Frontier Marshal, June 1, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 121)
    Story: Stuart N. Lake
    Screenplay: Sam Hellman
    Director: [Allan Dwan]
    Producer: [Sol Wurtzel]
    Actors: [Randolph Scott Nancy Kelly Cesar Romero]
    Setting: Tombstone, Arizona
  - Frontiersman, August 13, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 122)
    Story: [Clarence E. Mulford]
    Screenplay: Harrison Jacobs [Norman Houston]
    Actors: William Boyd George Hayes Russell Hayden
  - Fury at Firecreek, September 12, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 123)
    Screenplay: Calvin Clements
  - The Gambler, November 19, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 124)
    Screenplay: Jim Byrnes
    Director: [Dick Lowery]
    Producer: [Ken Kregen]
    Actors: Kenny Rogers [Bruce Boxleitner Clu Gulager]
    Production company: [Kragen & Company]
    Notes: written on cover "Neil Summers as 'Polo'"
  - Garden of Evil, November 27, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 125)
    Story: [Fred Freiberger William Tunberg]
    Screenplay: Frank Fenton [Richard Breen]
    Director: [Henry Hathaway]
    Producer: [Charles Brackett]
    Actors: [Gary Cooper Susan Hayward Richard Widmark]
    Setting: Mexico
    Notes: filmed in Mexico
  - Gauntlet, January 31, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 126)
    Screenplay: Dennis Shryack Michael Butler
    Director: Clint Eastwood
    Producer: Robert Daley
    Actors: Clint Eastwood Sondra Locke Pat Hingle
    Setting: Phoenix, Arizona, Twentieth century
  - The Gay Caballero, May 16, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 127)
    Story: Walter Bullock Albert Duffy
    Screenplay: Albert Duffy [John Larkin]
    Director: Otto Brower
    Producer: [Walter Morosco (assoc) Ralph Dietrich (assoc)]
    Actors: Cesar Romero Sheila Ryan Chris-pin Martin
    Notes: Cisco Kid series. Working title: Ghost of the Cisco Kid.
  - Ghost of Zorro, March 23, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 128)
    Screenplay: Royal Cole William Lively Sol Shor
    Director: Fred C. Brannon
    Producer: Franklin Adreon (assoc)
    Actors: Clayton Moore Pamela Blake Roy Barcroft
    Notes: Has scene by scene and frame by frame description.
  - Girl of the Golden West, September 1, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 129)
    Screenplay: Isabel Dawn Boyce De Gaw
    Director: [Robert Z. Leonard]
    Producer: [William Anthony McGuire]
    Actors: [Jeanette MacDonald Nelson Eddy Walter Pidgeon]
    Setting: California, 1839
    Type: Temporary
  - The Glory Guys, 1965 release (Box 19, Folder 130)
    Story: Hoffman Birney
    Screenplay: Sam Peckinpah
    Director: [Arnold Laven]
    Producer: [Arnold Laven Arthur Gardner Jules Levy]
    Actors: [Tom Tryon Harve Presnell Senta Berger]
    Production company: Bristol Pictures
  - The Godchild, September 16, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 131)
    Story: [Peter B. Kyne]
    Screenplay: Ron Bishop
    Director: [John Badham]
    Actors: [Jack Palance Jack Warden Keith Carradine]
    Distributor: ABC - Movie of the Week
    Type: Final shooting script
    Notes: "11/26/74", "Richard Hack" written on cover. Working title: The Three Godfathers. Remake of 1948 version
  - Goin' South, June 10, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 132)
    Story: [John Herman Shanner Al Ramrus]
    Screenplay: John Herman Shanner Al Ramrus [Allen Mandel Charles Shyer]
    Director: [Jack Nicholson]
    Producer: [Harry Gittes Harold Schneider]
    Actors: [Jack Nicholson Mary Steenbergen Christopher Lloyd]
    Setting: Mexican border, 1866
  - Gold Train, August 6, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 133)
    Story: Stephen Longstreet
    Screenplay: Stephen Longstreet
    Production company: Fred Messenger Productions
    Type: Revised version
  - The Good Guys and the Bad Guys, September 9, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 134)
    Screenplay: Dennis Shryack Ronald M. Cohen
    Director: Burt Kennedy
    Producer: [Dennis Shryack Ronald M. Cohen]
    Actors: Robert Mitchum David Carradine Tina Louise
    Production company: Robert Goldstein Productions
  - The Great Cowboy Race, April 24, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 135)
    Screenplay: Abram S. Ginnes
  - The Great Northfield, Minnesota Raid, February 21, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 136)
    Screenplay: Philip Kaufman
    Director: [Philip Kaufman]
    Producer: Frank Price [Jennings Lang]
    Actors: [Cliff Robertson Robert Duvall Luke Askew]
    Setting: Missouri; Minnesota
  - The Great Northfield, Minnesota Raid, October 21, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 137)
    Director: Philip Kaufman
    Producer: Jennings Lang
    Actors: Cliff Robertson Robert Duvall Luke Askew
    Type: Third revision
    Notes: text fully annotated, "R. Milton" on cover.
  - The Gun Fighter, June 9, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 138)
    Story: [William Bowers Andre de Toth]
    Screenplay: William Bowers William Sellers
    Director: [Henry King]
    Producer: [Nunnally Johnson]
    Actors: [Gregory Peck Helen Westcott Millard Mitchell]
  - Gun For A Coward, November 23, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 139)
    Screenplay: H. Wright Campbell
    Director: [Abner Biberman]
    Producer: [William Alland]
    Actors: Fred MacMurray Jeffrey Hunter [Janice Rule]
    Production company: Universal-International Pictures
    Distributor: Universal-International Pictures
    Setting: cattle country
    Notes: With Revisions.
  - The Gun Hawk, February 20, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 140)
    Story: Richard Bernstein Max Steeber
    Screenplay: Jo Heims
    Director: [Edward Ludwig]
    Producer: [Richard Bernstein]
    Actors: [Rory Calhoun Rod Cameron Ruta Lee]
    Production company: Bern-Field Productions
    Distributor: [Allied Artists]
    Setting: Baxter
    Type: Cutting
    Notes: Includes prop lists, cutting tabs. Covered in comments. Shooting schedule on verso.
  - Gun Notches, October 17, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 141)
    Screenplay: Ed Earl Repp
  - Gun Smoke Valley (Box 20, Folder 142)
    Notes: "1st script submitted by O.D." Carbon copy.
  - Gun Town, June 14, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 143)
    Director: Wallace Fox
    Producer: Wallace Fox
    Actors: Kirby Grant Louise Currie Fuzzy Knight
  - A Gunfight, 1971 release (Box 21, Folder 144)
    Screenplay: Harold Jack Bloom
    Director: Lamont Johnson
    Producer: Ronald Lubin Harold Jack Bloom
    Actors: Kirk Douglas Johnny Cash Jane Alexander
    Production company: Bryna Productions
  - Gunman's Code, May 9, 1946 (Box 21, Folder 145)
    Story: [Arthur St. Claire Sherman Lowe]
    Producer: [Wallace Fox (assoc)]
    Actors: [Kirby Grant Fuzzy Knight Jane Adams]
    Production company: [Universal]
    Distributor: [Universal]
    Type: Original screenplay
  - Gunman's Code, July 24, 1946 (Box 21, Folder 146)
    Type: Continuity breakdown
    Notes: "Willie Cook" on front cover
  - The Guns of Fort Petticoat, March 29, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 147)
    Story: C. William Harrison
    Screenplay: Walter Doniger
    Producer: Harry Joe Brown
    Actors: Audie Murphy Kathryn Grant Hope Emerson
    Production company: Brown-Murphy Pictures
    Notes: Notes on cover: "Hope Emerson - Hannah" and "To casting"
  - The Hallelujah Trail, May 27, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 148)
    Story: Bill Gulick
    Director: John Sturges
    Producer: John Sturges
    Actors: Burt Lancaster Lee Remick Jim Hutton
    Production company: Mirisch-Kappa Productions
    Setting: Colorado, 1867
    Type: Combined Continuity
  - The Hallelujah Trail (Subtitle: The Hallelujah Train), March 18, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 149)
  - Hands Across the Border, 1944 release (Box 21, Folder 150)
    Screenplay: Bradford Ropes J. Benton Cheney
    Director: Joseph Kane
    Producer: Harry Grey
    Actors: Roy Rogers Ruth Terry Guinn Williams
  - Hang 'em High, January 20, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 151)
    Screenplay: Leonard Freeman Mel Goldberg
    Director: Ted Post (Sergio Leone)
    Producer: Leonard Freeman
    Actors: Clint Eastwood Inger Stevens Ed Begley
  - The Hangman, September 8, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 152)
    Screenplay: Dudley Nichols
    Director: [Michael Curtiz]
    Producer: [Frank Freeman, Jr.]
    Actors: [Robert Taylor Fess Parker Tina Louise]
  - Hangman's Knot, March 3, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 153)
    Screenplay: Roy Huggins
    Director: [Roy Huggins]
    Producer: [Harry Joe Brown]
    Actors: [Randolph Scott Donna Reed Claude Jarman, Jr.]
    Production company: Scott - Brown
    Setting: Nevada Territory, 1865
    Type: First estimating draft
    Notes: Working title: The Outlanders
  - Hard-Boiled, January 29, 1926 (Box 22, Folder 154)
    Story: Charles Darnton
    Screenplay: Shannon Fife [Charles Darnton John Stone]
    Director: J. G. Blystone
    Producer: J. G. Blystone
    Actors: Tom Mix Helene Chadwick William Lawrence
    Type: First version
  - The Hard Road, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 155)
    Screenplay: Douglas Heyes Roy Erwin
    Notes: "Frank Cooper Associates Agency" stamp.
  - Haunted Ranch, 1942- 1943 (Box 22, Folder 156)
    Story: [Arthur Hoerl]
    Director: Robert Tansey
    Actors: John King David Sharpe Max Terhune
    Production company: Range Busters, Inc.
    Distributor: Monogram
    Setting: Colorado
    Notes: Range Busters series. Working title: Ridin' Double.
  - Hawaii, [1966 release] (Box 22, Folder 157)
    Story: James A. Michener
    Screenplay: [Dalton Trumbo Daniel Taradash]
    Producer: [Walter Mirisch]